what in geography in chemistry in mathematics
что по географии по химии по математике
in
по
what in physical education I'm smarter in
чём по физкультуре я умней по
sports
спорту
Hello They tell me You're the one giving me Stream, she's
Привет Мне говорят Ты это ты мне Стрим
sitting Stream leading Yes, you're
ведёшь се сидит Стрим веду Да
showing What kind of Russians Yes And you
показываешь Какие русские Да А вы
Ukrainians are smart
украинцы умные
Neda Uh-
Неда
huh And you're smart Yes, let's do it, let's do it, let's
Угу А Вы умные Да вот давай давай давай
do
сделаем ба
it  that in geography in
давай что по географии по химии по
chemistry in mathematics in
математике по
World Cup in physical education I am smarter in sports in
ЧМ по физкультуре я умней по спорту по
physical education you are smarter than you at
физкультуре ты умней умнее тебя по
least less Let's
крайней мене Давай Давай попробуем по
try in physical education Okay
Давай попробуем по физкультуре О'кей
uh Where is the muscle I am in modern
ээ Где находится мышца я по современной
in modern physical education I have in
по современной физкультуре У мене по
modern physical education  this For example, what
современной физкультуре это Например что
is modern
такое современная
physical education modern in football
физкультура современная по по футболу
smarter in tennis smarter in basketball in
умнее по теннису умнее по баскетболу по
volleyball in freestyle wrestling smarter and what is your
волейболу по вольной борьбе умнее а ты
question okay let's
по чём вопрос хорошо давай давай
look at football in volleyball for this
посмотрим по футболу по волейболу по это
Let's talk about football yes uh what is the size of a
Давай по футболу да ээ какой размер
football
футбольного
field size Yes I knew  I don’t remember Now
поля размер Да я знал не помню Сейчас
let’s move on Well, damn it’s already about
давай дальше Ну всё ты блин уже по
football, what what come on, what size
футболу что что давай давай какой размер
what size is the football field You know
какой размер футбольного поля Ты знаешь
35 m by 46 m yeah How many players are there on the
35 м на 46 м ага Сколько игроков на
football field game 11 on one side
футбольном поле игра 11 с одной стороны
one on the other side I won everything That’s
один с другой стороны всё я выиграл Вот
it  It was a difficult question for you,
это у тебя сложный вопрос был
of course, now I’m asking you
конечно теперь я теперь я тебе задаю
a question: Yes, what is the diameter of the ball in
вопрос Да какой какой диаметр мяча в
lawn
большом
tennis, in lawn tennis,
теннисе в большом
the diameter of
теннисе диаметр
cha I don’t play tennis, I play
ча я в большой теннис не играю я играю в
table tennis, in
настольный теннис ме
lawn tennis, the diameter of the ball is 3 inches in
в большом теннисе диаметр мяча 3 дюйма в
table tennis, the diameter of the ball is 1
настольном теннисе диаметр мяча 1
inch inch you know how much is a centimeter
дюйм дюйм знаешь сколько это сантиметр
Estimate
Прикинь
Estimate Please tell me to answer the question
Прикинь Скажи пожалуйста на вопрос
that Russia will win Ukraine
та Россия выиграет Украину
part of the Kursk region and come to terms with the fact
часть Курской области и смирилась с тем
that it I think Russia will already
что она Я думаю Россия уже
lose you think so seriously Yes
проиграет ты так серьёзно думаеш Да
further on Let's then let's go on in sports
дальше по Давай то давай мы по спорту
further Come on on
дальше Давай по
sports come on come on  in sports So
спорту давай давай давай по спорту Так
what is it in What is it in
что такое в Что такое в
gymnastics bringo for gymnastics I do
гимнастике бринго за гимнастику я вообще
n’t know anything at all I understand about football Yes
ничего не знаю Поня поня про футбол Да
uh what kind of move in football
ээ какой Какой приём в футболе
is called double
называется двойной
Dual Dual double Dual
Дуал Дуал двойной Дуал
Yes I mean double Dual double Dual Yes I
Да в смысле двойной Дуал двойной Дуал Да
don’t know First time taco look yes  look
не знаю Первый раз тако смотри да смотри
Dual Dual is when there is a pair of these
Дуал Дуал - это когда идёт пара этих
football players, one passes and the other
футболистов один передаёт пас и другой
kind of shoots, it’s called Dual
типа пробивает это называется Дуал
double Dual is when two pairs of
двойной Дуал - это когда идут две пары
football players go, one on the right flank,
футболистов один по правому флангу
for example, one pair on the right flank, the
например одна пара по правому флангу
other either on the left or left flanks
другая либо по левому либо левый фланги
center Yes, one passes  from the first dual he
центр Да один передаёт с первого дуала
passes a pass to the second pair Yes and the second one
передаёт пас на второго Да и второй
passes the pass to the
передаёт пас
second pair That is, in the second dual and
в вторую пару То есть во второй Дуал и
this one passes here and shoots, that is, a
этот передаёт сюда и пробивает то есть
combination of four of the two duals Uh-huh
комбинация из четырёх из двух дуалок
well done,
Угу молодец
I’m just saying, well, I played football
сказать я просто ну я занимался футболом
professionally Yes, my leg is a little
профессионально Да немножко нога у меня
weak  my leg was injured, so I don’t
у меня нога травмирована была поэтому не
play, so you just see in
играю так что просто у вас видишь в
Russia how they just play
России как ну там просто играете в
football there, but seriously, there are whole
футбол да а серьёзно то есть есть целые
combinations, they have certain
комбинации они имеют определённые
names. Yes, there is a triplet, you know
названия Да вот есть триплет знаешь что
what a triplet is in football, a triplet, a
такое триплет в футболе триплет
triplet, a triplet is a combination  from
триплет триплет - это комбинация из про
what kind of football are you talking about, is it
какой именно футбол вообще говоришь про
big big big football
большой ли большой большой футбол
big football Yes, a triplet is when
большой футбол Да триплет - это когда
there are three of these three players so they
идёт три этих три игрока так они
play a split scoop on three, yes, that
разыгрывают распа совку на трёх да то
is, this is a classic combination. That is,
есть это классическая комбинация То есть
it’s like a Dual only Dual for two Yes, this is a
это как Дуал только Дуал вдвоём Да это
pass and  a kick and a triplet is when there are three people. Yes, a
пас и удар а триплет - это когда трое Да
pass goes to one, a pass from him to the second one and
идёт пас одному пас от него второму и
it’s a triplet. Well, come on, if that’s the case, you
пробивает это триплет Ну давай если так
understand better, if you
вут боле хорошо разбираешься если ты
played football, I’ll ask you a simple question,
футбол играл я тебе задам простой вопрос
come on, let’s look, look, come on, what do
давай давай смотри смотри Давай я по что
you care about sports already?  four or
тебя по спорту уже я тебе четыре или
five in short already let's listen let's
пять короче уже давай слушай давай
in short some other topics
короче ещё другие какие-то темы
Let's see let's
Посмотрим
try Well let's tell you In general
попробуем Ну давай тебе говори Вообще
what topic ho what topics do you
какую тему хо какие темы тебе
like any if I know something about it
нравятся любая если я про неё буду
I'll tell you if I don't know I'll
что-то знать я тебе скажу если не знае
say I don't know damn it  yes Well,
скажу что не знаю блин да Ну ну давай
go ahead, just choose, I, as a smarter person,
Выбери просто я как человек более умный
allow you to choose the first
тебе разрешаю выбрать первую
topic. Do you think
тему я ты как считаешь
Ukraine needs this war at all? Why No Ukraine For peace, Ukraine
Украине Зачем Нет Украина За мир Украина
wants Victory Why do we need war?
хочет Победы Зачем нам война Угу а то
Russia, let
правительство на вам это Россия давайте
us come to Ukraine, we will open your border,
к нам к Украине мы вашу границу откроете
we will transfer this to NATO so that this Russia yes yes it
мы НАТО переведём чтобы эту Россию да да
will be yes yes it
так и будет да
will be so yes you think so
да будет так да ты так считаешь
yes Oh God what is on your mind
да Ой Господи что у вас на уме у
Ukrainians Damn I don’t know what you
украинцев Блин я не знаю на что вы
are hoping for let’s look come on  not about
надеетесь давай смотри давай не про
the war, let's talk about life, about sports,
войну давай вот о жизненном о спорте
come on, come on, let's not talk
давай давай давай давай давай не будем
about the war. What sports do you still
про войну Какие виды спорта тебе ещё
need? sports
нужно виды спорта
Yes basketball Let's basketball Yes Bubble
Да баскетбол Давай баскетбол Да Бабл
jumping in basketball What is
джампинг в баскетболе Что такое
Bubble Jum ball Jumping I don't know I don't know
Бабл Jum бал Jumping не знаю не знаю
look jumping is a throw  with with this with a jump
смотри джампинг - это заброс с с этим с
Jump - this is jumping in English
прыжком Jump - это прыгать по-английски
Yes, jumping is when they jump up and
Да джампинг - это когда подпрыгивают и
in short throw it, I understand what you mean
короче закидывают я по я понял о чём ты
and Bubble Jumping is
а Бабл Jumping - это
when one jumps up
когда один подпрыгивает
and they think they are going to jump up to
да думают его идут его подпрыгивают
block him because they think that he
блокировать потому что думают что он
will  and he gives his partner the ball, which is
будет ть а он даёт напарнику мяч который
also under that is, the two of them jump, I
тоже под то есть Они двое подпрыгивают
saw this. This is a very difficult technique.
вот видел такое Это очень сложный приём
Yes, a jump of two, one with the ball, of the one who is
Да прыжок двое один с мячом того что с
blocking with the ball near the basket, and he in a
мячом блокирует возле корзины а он в
jump passes this bubble like
прыжке передаёт э вот этот баббл типа
Bubble - it’s like in
Бабл - это как
Russian  bubble bubble tee here's a ball this is a
по-русски пузырь пузырь ти вот шарик это
bubble type Bubble jumping type passing
баббл типа Бабл джампинг типа передача
during a jump like this When two people
во время прыжка вот этого Когда двое
jump one throws the ball in a jump and
прыгают один перекидывает мяч в прыжке и
he scores and he was blocked this and
тот забивает а его блокировали этого и
all the chickens that you are talking to me on video more than once
всё кур что ты по видео со мной не раз
that you know that you  you
разговариваешь что ты в курсе что ты со
talk to me on video more than once, I
мной по видео не раз разговариваешь я же
remember the first time you had no hands, like you were
помню первый раз ты с без рук типа ты
standing talking to me in the toilet no yes
стоял общался со мной в туалете нет да
no
нет
yes You are now starting to mock
да Это ты сейчас уже начинаешь стебать
me even though this didn’t happen
меня при том что это этого не было было
You also told me that you remember when I
Ты ещё рассказывал что помнишь когда я
you came across it in the evening three times in a row
тебе попадался вечером три раза подряд
three times in a row yes
три раза подряд да
No, not three more so the first time, look the
Нет не три больше так первый раз смотри
first time you went to the toilet I That’s
первый раз ты пошёл по в туалет я Та ты
what I’m saying And how are you without hands you
что по я говорю А как ты без рук ты
say like, well, like it’s
говоришь типа ну так Типа оно
not there It’s probably me  confused with
само нет Это наверно ме нано перепутал с
someone I when if I communicate I when
кем-то я во когда если общаюсь Я когда
if I communicate with someone I never go to the toilet
если общаюсь с кем-то Я никогда в туалет
on camera Go into the bucket Show me In short, I’m
на камеру Зайди в парашу Покажи Короче я
there now then you showed me a
вот сейчас туда потом ты мне показывал
window like the view from the window you said that you are a
окно типа вид из окна ты сказал что ты
worker there now filming  apartment
рабочий там сейчас снимаешь квартиру
Like you were doing something yes yes yes yes I
Типа вы что-то делали да да да да я ж
remember Show the parasha I now
помню Покажи парашу я сейчас
recognize the parasha Yes I don’t want to show I got
узнаю парашу Да не не хочу показывать
it Okay okay What other sports are
понял Ладно хорошо Какие ещё виды спорта
you interested in You stream I don’t want to
тебя интересуют Ты Стрим ведёшь не хочу
show it although there Everything is fine good
показывать хотя там Всё нормально хорошо
What other sports are you interested in
Какие ещё виды спорта тебя
interested in table tennis table
интересуют настольный теннис настольный
tennis Yes Cool And you played
теннис Да Прикольно А ты играл
table tennis I I just play everything
настольный теннис я я во всё играю
I just these how can I tell you these are
просто я вот эти как тебе сказать это
jumps not jumps I first of all I don’t jump
джампы не джампы я во-первых Я не прыгаю
because
так как
professional athletes I don’t
профессиональные спортсмены я это не
study this But I play everything  I
изучаю А в это я во всё играю во всё
can do everything Well, what about table tennis? You know,
умею Ну что настольно теннис Ты знаешь
for example, you played doubles tennis, like
например ты играл в парный теннис типа
when two and a couple play against a couple. I played and played a couple against a
когда двое и пару на пару Я играл и пару
couple for first place and so I
на пару играл за первое место и так
understood solo what it is in table tennis,
понял что такое в настольном теннисе
knowing that in Russian the words you say are  There
зна это по-русски слова говоришь которые
are so many of us in Russia. I
у нас в России я допустим сколько Вот
play steel tennis.
занимаюсь играл на стальном теннисе у
We’ve never even heard anyone say this before.
нас такого ни разу даже никто не
I understand that it can be called
сова я понял у вас оно может называться
penetration, like maybe it’s called something else.
проникновение типа ну может по-другому
But I don’t know those
называется Но вот это я не знаю таких
words. Come on, what else do you know?  Yes, look,
слов Давай А что ещё знаешь Да смотри
eat This is when there is a strike with and with a racket
поешь Это когда идёт удар с и ракеткой
you catch the ball almost to the opponent’s side
догоняешь мяч почти на сторону соперника
That is, you hit the net with a racket Yes, but
То есть ты сеешь сетку ракеткой Да но
you get it without hitting the table So and you
доводишь ты не отбивая стола Так а ты
almost catch it That’s how it just
ловишь его почти Вот как он только
crosses
пересекает
your half, or almost like that and you
твою половину так либо почти так и
catch up but not  crossing the plane of the
догоняешь но не пересекая плоскость
grid Top spin you know what
сетки Топ спин знаешь что
it is Yes, damn you,
такое ж Да блин ты что
you're screwed By the way, look at it Well,
капец Ты кстати посмотри Ну ты
you know the terms in English, you see
по-английски ты знаешь термины видишь
because and you say that you don’t know in
потому что а ты говоришь что не знаешь в
Russia, well, here we just have what you
России ну у нас просто то что ты
say, we’ve never had anyone like that  didn’t
говоришь у нас такого ни разу никто не
say it at least less at
произносил по край менее по крайней
least I didn’t hear it from anyone Although I
менее я не слышал ни от кого Хотя я во
took part in many tennis competitions in
многих на соревнованиях участвовал по
Russia and no one said anything like that,
России по теннису и никто такого не
I’m only hearing it from you for the first time
произносил я от тебя только первый раз
I didn’t even hear it from the coach
слышу Даже даже от тренера я этого не
And who do you have  you are a coach who is a
слышал А кто у тебя у тебя тренер кто
master of sports, a candidate
мастер спорта кандидат
who is a coach, a master of sports, but I have already
кто тренер тренер мастер спорта но я уже
trained, I will tell you how long I have been practicing
занимался скажу сколько я занимался 7
tennis for 7 years,
лет теннисом насто
this was when it was when I started from the
это было когда это когда я получается с
fifth grade and now for how many
пятого класса и вот сейчас уже сколько я
years I have probably not been
уже наверно лет наверно во уже не
practicing for years Well, in general  In short, when I was there,
занимаюсь Ну в общем короче когда я был
I was training and I was trained, I
я занимался и меня вот тренировали я
went to competitions in Russia,
ездил на соревнованиях по России
I participated in table
участвовал по настольному
tennis, yes, yes, what besides tennis,
теннису да да а что кроме тенниса еут
I now play purely as a hobby.
я сейчас чисто играю так уже как хобби
That is, I don’t practice now, because
То есть я сейчас не занимаюсь Потому что
now I have purely work and just  I
сейчас у меня чисто работа просто и
never have time, only when I come back from a
некогда бывает только когда приеду из
business trip, let’s say, to my city and
командировки допустим в свой город и
play football with the guys, and well, I
погоняю с мужиками футбол а так ну
did freestyle wrestling. Cool And what other
занимался Прикольно А какими ещё
sports did I play? Chess,
занимался видами спорта Шахматы
maybe chess, no, I haven’t done that,
может шахматами нет этим не занимался
I can play chess, but I can play bad, I
шахмата умею играть но плохо шки тоже
can play bad too, and
умею играть тоже плохо
so on  chess I love chess but it’s
вот а так шахматы Я люблю шахматы но это
not my thing That is,
не моё То есть я как с каким-нибудь
I can play with some ordinary player, but
обычным игроком я могу поиграть но так
no, but an unusual player is what it is that
нет а необычный игрок это какой там что
he has four hands Well, no, well, not an ordinary
у него четыре руки Ну нет ну не обычный
one who already plays well
который уже достаточно уже хорошо играет
enough, understands tactics, is excellent
достаточно тактику понимает прекрасны
who really already have medals in
которые действительно уже есть медали на
competitions, I’ve been to a lot Yes, with such a
соревнованиях много побывал Да с таким
game it even makes sense, of course I understood who
даже смысла игра понятное дело понял кто
Koch is in table
такой коч в настольном
tennis, I’ll tell you right away for table
теннисе сразу тебе скажу за настольной
tennis I don’t watch athletes who
тенниса я спортсменов не смотрю кто
is in the table shadow always at
такой в настольном тени всегда на
competitions Who is a
соревнованиях Кто такой
coach Koch coach
коач коч коуч
coach I don’t know  again, you have your own, which ones are
коуч не знаю у вас опять же свои какие
you exactly about tennis or about
ты именно м сам про теннис или про
players burn a
игроков гори
player is a coach trainer in tennis in
игрока это коуч тренер в теннисе в
table tennis the player's coach
настольном теннисе тренер игрока
is called a
называется
coach I don’t know about well now you maybe have
коуч не знаю о ну сейчас ты ты может
n’t played for a long time Because now new
давно не играл Потому что сейчас новые
terminology has been adopted by the rules of the
терминологии принята правила
International Federation yes
международной Федерации да
is it possible and how new is it?
возможно и насколько она новая это
Technology Technology or terminology
Технология Технология или терминология
technology, namely this rule or
технология а именно это правило или что
whatever, well, it definitely already exists, it seems to me
там ну лет се точно уже есть мне кажется
Maybe maybe you have Russia, you have Russia, they haven’t
Может может у вас Россия у вас Россия не
implemented
имплементировать
yet, they played by the old rules, you know,
играли ещё по старым правилам понимаешь
well, I’ve always played this way for how long I’ve been playing.  I always
ну я всегда вот сколько я играл Я всегда
played according to the old rules, always up to 11
играл по старым правилам всегда до 11
points in two serves, yes, but this is according to the new
очков по две подачи да а это по новым
rules. By the way, if Why Russia doesn’t
правилам Кстати если Почему Россия не
accept the new rules,
принимает новые правила
you know, I don’t know, because according to modern
знаешь не знаю потому что по современным
rules they play
правилам играт до
until the Russians lose 11 points. Yes, they take a
когда у Россиян порвут 11 очков Да берут
new Russian with a dm
нового россияна с дм
point.  you're like outplayed in tennis
очком я тебя походу Переиграл в теннис
don't let me tear you
не давай я тебя порвал
up so skiki we came up with new
бы так скики мы придумали новых
terms double double
терминов двойной дабл
double dub that's so double double that's
двойной даб это так двойной дабл это
so 11
так 11
points 11 points this is a football
очков 11 очков это футбольная
team from Russia write to my Telegram
команда из России пись на мий Telegram
directly at once axis vin and
прямо зараз ось вин а
popk tse more and more  respectfully YouTube has occupied
попк це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through skarg orki new ban and even more rich
нас через скарг орки ньй бан и дуже
video I don’t show people often I don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams for this purpose for
показуе информация про стримы тому для
Mali operational link
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
to write directly at the same time and while there in telegra
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okm video also tezh Tsikava and Korisna
окм вдео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and I’m sorry  you trimati
информация и ми повинни з вами тримати
Lenten operational connection
постный оперативный звязок
nezalezhno in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine subscribe
YouTube Слава Украине подпишись